{"data":[{"question":"Karajan was the first person recognizing her extraordinary musical gift.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"was","b":"first","c":"recognizing","d":"musical","answer":"3","explain":"- Recognizing-> to recognize","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Its lack of irregular verbs makes Esperanto an unique language.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Its","b":"verbs","c":"makes","d":"an","answer":"4","explain":"- An-> a","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Perhaps no one will ever know what did happened that fateful night.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Perhaps","b":"ever","c":"did","d":"that","answer":"3","explain":"- Did-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"There was another revolutionary in microchip technology in 1971.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"was","b":"revolutionary","c":"technology","d":"in","answer":"2","explain":"- Revolutionary-> revolution","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"No one stands a chance of beating Mansell in this year's champion.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"stands","b":"of","c":"this year's","d":"champion","answer":"4","explain":"- Champion-> championship","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"If he had done his homework, his parents might have let him to go to the party.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"had done","b":"parents","c":"let","d":"to go","answer":"4","explain":"- To go-> go","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"In the event, the extra insurance we took out wasn't be necessary.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"In","b":"insurance","c":"took","d":"be","answer":"4","explain":"- Be->x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"He speaks more persuasive than his brother does.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"speaks","b":"more","c":"persuasive","d":"does","answer":"3","explain":"- Persuasive-> persuasively","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"He forgotten about the gun until he got home.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"forgotten","b":"gun","c":"until","d":"got","answer":"1","explain":"- Forgotten-> forgot","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Alan worked too hard at the office, and this led to his ill.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"worked","b":"hard","c":"this","d":"ill","answer":"4","explain":"- Ill->illness","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"}]}